=== Contact form builder FormForAll - Facebook connect, Responsive design, double opt-in, multilingual === 
Contributors: FormForAll
Donate link: http://www.formforall.com/
Tags: formforall, form4all, form for all, form, forms, online forms, web forms, form builder, lead generation, contact form, contact forms, surveys, order forms, online order forms, online surveys, registration forms, event registration forms, lead generation form, multilingual forms, multilingual, multilingual online forms, social login, Facebook connect, Facebook, responsive design, double opt-in, Catalan, Chinese (simple), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English (US),English (UK), French, German, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Polish, Portuguese, Slovak, Spanish, Russian, Turkish

Requires at least: 3.5.1
Tested up to: 3.5.2
Stable tag: 1.0

Drag and Drop easy interface. Tens of predefined fields, including Connect with Facebook. Multilingual. Responsive design forms, double opt-in.


== Description ==

Our FormForAll plugin and widget allows you to easily insert your FomForAll forms into your sidebar and to embed them into your Wordpress site.

For this plugin to work, you need:

* to open a FormForAll account: signup for free at http://www.formforall.com and test our Free plan.
* to use our User API key.

Create your forms in seconds:

* Easy Drag and Drop interface.
* Multilingual form: build your form in your own language and have it displayed in 18 western and Asian languages : Catalan, Chinese (simple), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English (US),English (UK), French, German, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Polish, Portuguese, Slovak, Spanish, Russian, Turkish.
* An extensive selection of forms fields: predefined ones (name, address, identity, credit card, date / time, ...), customized fields (text, radio buttons, check boxes, file uploads).
* Connect with Facebook: insert our Connect with Facebook field into your form in 2 seconds instead of days!
* Double opt-in: when your web users submit their form, an e-mail with a verification link is sent to their declared e-mail address. When the web user clicks on the link in the e-mail, we check and pass the information on to you.

Settings options:

* All forms are in responsive design (for Smartphone, tablet and PC)
* Insertion of your logo.
* Choice of font, size, color, custom CSS.
* SSL, RSA key, Captcha.
* Notification emails: we can send you an e-mail as soon as a form has been submitted. You can then export submitted data using your control panel. If you need submitted data on a real time basis, use our API. 
* Confirmation emails: every time a form is submitted, we can send a confirmation e-mail on your behalf to your web users. 
* Form submission message or redirection: a default message can be displayed to the user once the form is submitted, or the user can be redirected to the URL of your choice.

Publish your form online:

* With a hosted URL.
* With our JavaScript, that you just have to copy / paste, wich will embed your form on a HTML page of your site.

Collect submissions data of your web users

* By Export CSV or with our Records API (full documentation step by step provided).
* Activity reports. 

== Installation ==

* .1. Open a free FormForAll account: signup for free at http://www.formforall.com
* .2. Through your Wordpress menu, click on Plugins and type FormForAll on the search box
* .3. Once you have found our FormForAll plugin, click on Install now
* .4. A new window opens. Click on Install now.
* .5. Click on Activate Plugin. You should see our Plugin on your Plugins' list.
* .6. Look at your wordpress toolbar, our logo icon should have appeared at the right of the toolbar menu. Click on the icon.
"* .7. If a new window opens with the message : ""Parameters have not been set correctly"", go to next step, otherwise skip to step 13."
"* .8. Click on the message ""Parameters have not been set correctly""."
"* .9. To use our API, you need to enter 2 parameters. To get them, click on the link ""To get an API key""."
* .10. You are now redirected to our site www.formforall.com. Log-in to your account, go to MY ACCOUNT and then to USER API KEY.
"* .11. On the USER API KEY window, you see the User ID and API key parameters that you have to copy on wordpress.Once copied on wordpress, click on ""Save changes""."
"* .12. A ""settings saved"" message should appear and confirm that your API parameters have been saved."
"* .13. You're done! A new window opens. All forms you have created on your www.formforall.com account appear there. Just select one form and click on ""Add a form"" to insert it whereever you want on your wordpress site!"




== Frequently Asked Questions ==
What do I need to do first ?
First open an account on www.formforall.com, we have a free and premium plans.


Where can I find my FormForAll User API key?

To get your FormForAll User API key, login to your FormForAll account
(https://www.formforall.com) then go to ‘My Account’ then to ‘User API key’.

== Screenshots ==

== Changelog ==

= 1.0 =
* Initial release.
